https://gaiconsultants.com/privacy-policy/

Careers
Search for:
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Revised Date: May 25, 2018
GAI Consultants, Inc. has developed this Privacy Statement out of respect for the privacy of visitors to our websites. Through this website, GAI Consultants, Inc. will collect information that can identify you and/or your activity. We will use your information to respond to requests you may make of us, and from time to time, we may refer to this information for other purposes.
Information that we collect
Whenever you visit our website, we will collect some information from you automatically, and some voluntarily.
We will collect the following information automatically:
The date and time of your visit
Click and visit data (what on the site interests you and how long you visit the site)
Browser information
We will collect the following information voluntarily:
Your name
Your e-mail address
Your company (optional)
Jobs at GAI Consultants
When you choose to post a resume to the careers section of the website and apply to become part of the GAI team, please note that you will be taken to a third-party URL (https://opportunities.gaiconsultants.com/) and these pages are branded as GAI.  The information you provide will be used solely for the purposes for which it is provided (including the processing of your application) and will be retained for such period as is necessary to comply with GAI’s legal and administrative requirements.
Uses of the information that we collect
We collect information about our website visitors for a number of reasons, including:
To improve the website experience for all visitors
To understand the demographics of our website visitors
To provide you with periodic information based on your interests
To consider you for a position at GAI (for information entered through the careers section of the website)
How we protect the information that we collect
The protection of the information that we collect from our site visitors is of the utmost importance to us and we take every reasonable measure to ensure that protection, including:
We keep automatically and voluntarily collected website data separate from voluntarily collected job data at all times
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption wherever we capture voluntarily provided job information
Use of cookies and other tracking technologies
Cookies are small files that a website may transfer to a user’s computer that reside there for either the duration of the browsing session (session cookies) or on a permanent (until deleted) basis (persistent cookies) that may be used to identify a user, a user’s machine, or a user’s behavior. We make use of cookies under the following circumstances and for the following reasons:
Compile data about site traffic to offer a better website experience
Understand and save visitor preferences for future visits
Third-party disclosure of the information that we collect
We do not sell or otherwise trade the Private Information that we collect from our site visitors at any point or under any circumstance. We do, on occasion share that information with business partners to ensure an ability to consistently provide service, or with government and other agencies where required by law. When we share such information, we ensure that the third parties with whom we share have policies and controls in place that are at least as stringent as our own.
Your Privacy Rights
You can always opt not to disclose information to us or request that we remove any stored personal information by completing the form on our Contact: Privacy Rights page.  Also, you can opt-out of receiving certain promotional or marketing communications from us at any time, by using the unsubscribe link in the email communications we send. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please complete the form on our Contact: Privacy Rights page and we will do our best to resolve your concerns.
Changes
From time to time we may modify and/or update this Privacy Statement and so encourage you to check back on a regular basis to determine if any changes have been made.
Home
About GAI
Company Overview
Corporate Responsibility
Leadership
Locations
Subsidiaries
Media Center
Search for:
Read:GAI’s Response to COVID-19
